Hello hello everyone how are you all so
we have made a video of the budget for you people
and according to what happened in each sector we
showed you which shares will benefit,
it was told what will happen in the system, it is
visible on the screen, if you have
not seen it then definitely watch it because after watching it
you will understand what to do in the portfolio,
whom to keep and why to leave it,
because in the same series we are
making the first video with you on your demand,
what are the benefits, what are the losses of dead or bad banks of PSU banks
and the government is
investing money, disinvesting, how will it
interact, you people said it is a very
eye-opener video, that too is
on your screen, definitely watch it, then you will
keep it correctly in the portfolio and
in that the third number is of the insurance sector, the only
difference here is that after hearing this, there is
excessive consumption of ghee and subscription,
in the last two days there was only one day rally, that
means it got stuck, so what happened after all, so let us
try to understand the thing
step by step so that you never get
stuck in the insurance sector and
can enjoy it to the fullest and we are going to post the next item, if
that also did not work then village
YouTube  Definitely subscribe to the channel and keep getting updates.
If you're worried
about breaking news, breaking news is
not a problem. It's important to understand things. You'll be able to
earn money. We'll have very good staff
salaries. We'll be able to manage things
and you'll automatically be compelled to press the share button with your own fingers.
This is my promise. So, the
biggest highlight of Ginger
this time was the insurance
sector, where it was announced to increase FD from 59% to
75%. It was also discussed to
disinvest in LIC and bring its IPO.
Now, as FD
increases, there will be an immediate cost inflow. And
here, foreign
investors in the firm will also be able to get ownership rights. So,
overall, the news is good,
no doubt. After this happens,
insurance pensions will also increase in India.
Currently, the insurance sector's GDP
contribution to the sector is 50%, and there's a strong
expectation of an increase in that too. Besides, the
increase in half the limit will
also have a positive impact on employment generation in this sector,
so that the insurance
companies that are running in losses  There is
hope of getting a release here too, so
because of all these and for all these reasons a
rally was seen in this city on the budget day, right, but then
what happened, how much time is there,
busy life, I don't know the answer in the comment box, so let
us tell you that this was
only till the budget day, after that a
decline was seen in the shares of the sector and a considerable loss was
felt, so
let us understand why this happened, so to
know this, first of all let us see how much share each
company has in the Indian insurance market so
that
your weight becomes absolutely clear about this tractor,
now here you will be seeing the data in
which it is a bit old, it
is of 2019, but it may not be showing such a big difference in G-20,
where only
LIC is the leader, after that the second number is of
HDFC Life, after that there is SBI,
right, there is SBI Life,
so in this way, but now
what is the government doing in this, don't know, what is LIC doing, it is
disinvesting, so some
private person will definitely buy a stake in it,
right, and now the immediate player has also
got a free discount, so in such a situation, LIC's share here  Not only will
they get the best of their established clients, but the
best business model can
also be expected. In such a situation,
you can imagine what level of competition a company with a
market share of 17.94 will face in front of a company having a shifting market share.
You can understand this in the language of very common people. If I am
saying something wrong, you can tell me.
Apart from this, the pudding of SBI Increase FD Increase
in the market is really an interesting
company. It is also beneficial
because 59% is already missing. So, is there a
59% holding in these companies?
So let's consider it one by one. Again, if I
come to my own, first of all, let's
look at the flashlight mixed foreign holding. The
form folding of HDFC Life is in
front of you. You will find that the holding is in front of you where
December 20th is 20.87. Correct,
understand carefully. The paste of increase is right in
front of you. But even after the face of increase, could
it have gone up to 59%? It did not remain. There is
something in it. After that, you
Look at ICICI Prudential, their holding increased
to 16.28%. Couldn't they have gone up even a quarter of an inch here? They
absolutely could have,
but they didn't even go after that. That means they themselves are the ones who are
not giving them the chit
that enabled them to take such a large
stake there. Now, if
you look at anyone else in the same way, whether it's
SBI Life or the market, you'll
see that Nepal
Wi-Fi's holding is roughly 20 to 24 percent. So,
why couldn't these companies entertain FIR as much as they will now? Those who will
now post 70 percent more after hearing this are something to
think about. And that's why I say
education is very important. If you
like the same thing, just
press the like button. Our model will also
boot inside. The thing here is that earlier,
Safai did not have the ownership rights, which will now be
eligible for I. It is often seen that
big companies use all the means to
aggressively expand their business.
Be it machines, packs,
investments or manpower, they never
lag behind and due to dollar relations, there is
no hesitation in making custom appointment products. So now Indian companies will not be
worried about their business, small
companies will not be afraid of them. They
rallied in an atmosphere of so much fear and panic
that you yourself are intelligent and this is the reason that
even after such a big news, the
rally of the insurance sector was curbed the next day. If you
agree with what I say, then do
tell me in the comment box. Also, tell me
which sector you want to know about.
Now I will speak from my heart.
Lastly, see, for me the insurance
sector is always good. Those who have
followed me for so long know that I have given HDFC
Life, ICICI Prudential, I don't know how many times I have given it to them. I have given it to them at
what lower rates. I have given it to them
whenever there has been a correction. I had
said it earlier and will say it today also that it should definitely
remain in our portfolio. But the
learning here is that
when you treat the situation only on the basis of one news,
you get stuck there. In the same way,
I made a video presenting the change, the
truth of PSU banks in the budget, that there  I got an eye
opening, you people gave me so much love,
so my effort is to make you face the truth,
establish you with the reality, where you
people laugh, where
Gurudev, so again my intention to say this is clear, this
insurance sector is very good for some other sector,
just because of that think but
running like this, but it is
not wise at all, so I hope you
liked it, if we are going to bring a similar eye opening
video of pharma, then
give love by liking, commenting and sharing, do the
work of a brother, thank you so much